We have to get the people of our country
of this country to love Israel more. I
have to tell you that. We have to do it.
We have to get them to love Israel more
because you have people that are Jewish
people that are great people. They don't
love Israel enough. You know that.
You [cheering] know that.
So you guys do know that he's like their
guy, right? And I don't just mean on a
political level. So this is what Joe
Biden took just to give you perspective.
This is what Joe Biden took from these
people.
And this is what Donald Trump took from
these people. And so when they say that
he's really special in their eyes, like
really special, like on a spiritual
level,
they're not kidding.
Christians, listen up. This is an award
they gave him and he took this award no
problem called the prince of peace.
Please, you go ahead. We love you, Mr.
President.
>> Thank you very much.
>> Please lead us.
Okay. Give thanks. Give thanks
to Hashem
for his work is good, his kindness
endures forever. Presented to President
Donald J. Trump for his extraordinary
and heroic efforts. I like that very
much.
To help the state of Israel and the
Jewish people.
He and his family should be blessed
eternally from the Israel Heritage
Foundation, July 10th, 2023. I want to
thank you very much. That's it.
>> [applause]
>> You must go to win.
Listen. Let Let me put it this way. If
we don't win, Israel's in big trouble. I
really do.
>> you're going to win. I mean it. Israel's
in big trouble here.
>> No, you're going to win. Thank you very
much.
And never mind the Tourette's with this
guy, but here's another award that they
gave him.
Mr. President, it's my pleasure to
specifically present to you
the Theodore Herzl Medallion.
Rarely given by the United States by the
Zionist Organization of America. We've
only given this to Lord Balfour, Winston
Churchill, President Truman, David
Ben-Gurion, Golda Meir,
and now we'll be giving it
to you. I'll I'll formally introduce
you.
And here's a very disturbing video of a
Jewish rabbi talking about Donald
Trump.
Current non-Jewish Messiah was chosen to
be of service to the Jewish people and
the Jewish Messiah.
President Trump's right ear was grazed
in a symbolic gesture of Exodus 21:6
where the Torah states that a servant
who wants to remain with his master
needs to have his right ear pierced.
Trump was designated as God's servant
and anointed one, just like Cyrus the
Great almost 2,400 years ago.
We have clarified in several videos that
the absolute deadline for the redemption
is by the end of the Jewish year 5,787,
which corresponds to October 2nd, 2027.
1,167
days from today.
Thus, the redemption will surely occur
during Donald Trump's tenure.
And I have good reason to believe Donald
Trump was chosen to be the one to redeem
the sins of Esau through offering his
assistance in rebuilding the holy temple
on the Temple Mount and establishing the
Jewish kingdom over all of mankind in
Jerusalem.
Perhaps it is no accident that the
numeric value of Donald Trump in Hebrew
is the same as Messiah son of David,
Mashiach ben David, 424.
However,
Donald Trump is mistaken if he thinks he
was chosen to make America great again.
He will no doubt do a lot of good things
to strengthen our economy, protect our
borders, and allow religious freedom to
flourish, but America will never become
a great country on its own.
Because Esau's days are numbered.
All our elite institutions and centers
of power and influence are rotten
through and through.
The majority of Americans under 30 who
are college educated and who are the
future leaders of America support the
vicious monsters of Hamas rather than
the holy and courageous soldiers of the
IDF.
No human being, even Donald Trump, can
reverse this. No.
The greatness of America does not lie
success.
America will be great when the Messiah
comes.
And the leader of this country, on
behalf of all the good people in this
country, will humbly present himself to
the Jewish Messiah and ask him to accept
the United States of America into a new
alliance of countries who accept the
leadership of the Messiah.
A new United Nations will replace the
current cesspool that goes by that
fraudulent name. A real United Nations
united to serve God, led by the Messiah
and based in Jerusalem.
And my feeling is that the United
States, under President Trump, will be
the first nation to join. So then the
question is, is Trump Jewish? And I
think he answers that question just
fine.
And these people do like Israel. Hold
on.
And he loves Israel, too. It's true.
I
NEED 2 SECONDS.
>> [applause]
>> 6 YEARS AGO I was up here.
And I said this is our first Jewish
president.
>> [applause]
>> It's true. Now he's the first Jewish
president to serve two
not not consecutive
presidencies. We thank you for
everything.
>> [music]